

## INTRODUCTION

With experience in the fields of graphic design, education and technology, I have found a suitable middle ground for my career to grow in the E-learning industry!

Full Name Erra Fazira Binte Osman

Age 27

Nationality Singaporean Availability January 2022

**Contact** +65 83219449

osman.erra@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Graphic Design
SCORM (Articulate Storyline)
Basic 2D Animation
Basic Video Editing
Basic Photography
Microsoft Office
LMS Management
ICT & Arts Training
Administrative Duties

# **Erra Osman**

# **E-Learning Content Developer**

#### PORTFOLIO



LINK
https://tinyurl.com/erraosman

#### EDUCATION

#### LASALLE COLLEGE OF THE ARTS

Diploma in Design Communication

August 2011 - September 2014

#### EXPERIENCES

#### **E-LEARNING CONTENT DEVELOPER**

ST Engineering e-Services Pte. Ltd. | Singapore

Jan 2021 - Present (1-year Contract)

As a Learning Content Developer working for the SAF, I was tasked to:

- Support CCDT Instructional Designers in the development of E-Learning content including graphical and video development.
- Work with SME to design engaging and informative E-Learning Content.
- Assist in fulfilling change requests or enhancements needed for existing and legacy e-Learning Content.
- Offer multimedia assistance whenever possible.
- Ensure content complies with LEARNet Content Governance.
- Maintain and improve the quality of products and services that meet objectives, needs and expectations of the TI.
- Deliver content developed within a given timeline.
- Work independently: Self-track tasks and report monthly.

With previous experience in E-learning content creation and the education industry, I was able to offer design solutions to improve the aesthetic of the existing e-learning content. From this work experience, I have sharpened my skills in content development, multimedia and graphic design to suit the learning needs of the SAF recruits (aged 18-30).

#### EXPERIENCES

#### **TEMP GRAPHICS ARTIST**

### Wizlearn Technologies Pte Ltd | Singapore

Aug 2020 - December 2020

As a Graphics Artist, I was in charge of:

- Designing layouts and graphic visuals for corporate e-learning content
- Creating simple animated videos for e-learning content using Adobe After Effects and Adobe Animate
- Other changes and amendments to existing e-learning content as assigned, using Adobe Illustrator, After Effects, Animate, Microsoft PowerPoint

#### **E-LEARNING DESIGNER**

# MIND STRETCHER EDUCATION | Singapore

Aug 2019 - Apr 2020

As an E-learning Designer, I was in charge of:

- Designing the interactivity and layout of e-learning resources using Articulate Storyline for Mathematics notes, quizzes and Mandarin Preschool ebooks.
- Creating digital illustrated assets to aid e-learning.
- Creating simple 2D animated GIFs to aid e-learning.

#### ICT EXECUTIVE & MULTIMEDIA TRAINER

# Wizlearn Technologies Pte Ltd | Singapore

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

- Keeping up with inventory and equipment loan
- Liaising with vendors for faulty equipment and purchase of equipment
- Assist Subject Head in budgeting for the purchase of IT equipment or software
- 1st level troubleshooting such as login issues, Microsoft Office issues, printer issues and replacement of faulty cables
- Photography and videography, video editing for school events and classroom recordings
- LMS portal duties: account creation, password reset, survey creation, create instructional slides for portal navigation
- Updating of the school website
- Setting up IT equipment in classrooms, exam halls and meetings
- Assist CCA Teachers in Infocomm Club
- Train in basic skills for Filmora and Canva
- Create learning materials for ICT Baseline

#### ICT EXECUTIVE & TRAINER

#### ACP Computer Training & Consultancy Pte Ltd | Singapore

Jul 2016 - Jan 2018

- Create lesson plans and conduct training for touch-typing, Microsoft Office programs, iMovie and Book Creator
- Integrate Cyber Wellness into ICT training
- Create worksheets and notes for ICT training
- Conduct lessons on ICT Baseline to primary school level

#### TESTIMONIAL

Erra joined our school as an ICT trainer in Mid 2017. Throughout her time in our school, she has displayed a positive attitude towards tasks that were given to her and approached any and all aspects of the work involved in teaching our pupils with dedication and eager anticipation. During the period that she was with us, she worked closely with the ICT Head of Department, Level head and teachers to plan and implement ICT baseline skills lessons and Cyber Wellness lessons for the pupils in the school. She also supported the Infocomm Club teachers to train the pupils in ICT skills.

In addition, she also helped to develop teaching resources such as lesson plans and handouts for the pupils. While teaching the ICT baseline lessons in the computer labs, she was always open to feedback on areas of improvements and willing to adjust any parts of the lessons that she thought could be improved. Erra also took the initiative to create many colourful, creative and effective posters that promoted the safe and responsible use of technology.

In closing, I would not hesitate to offer Erra a trainer position in your school/company were we to have an opening. Wherever she decides to accept a trainer position, I know with all confidence that she will do an outstanding job and become an asset to the school/company fortunate enough to receive her application for employment. Should you desire further information, please drop me an email at leng\_zhuyang@moe.edu.sg

Thank you.

Regards, Mr Joshua Lena

HOD (ICT), Fuchun Primary School • Tel: +65 63683925 • Fax: +65 63670117 • 23 Woodlands Ave 1, Singapore 739063 • http://www.fuchunpri.moe.edu.sq